Jenny Dinh

5483 Danbury Circle, Lake in the Hills, IL, 60156 (224) 622-7111 • jenny.p.dinh@gmail.com • www.github.com/jdinh3 www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-dinh-154a80116/

Summary:

A full-stack web developer with several years of work experience in Audio Engineering and Sales management who is eager to learning new technical skills and methods. Leveraged strong teamwork ethic and problem-solving skills to successfully create Full Stack applications in an agile environment. Enjoys using creativity and contributing new ideas to team environments.

Education:

Georgia Institute of Technology • Full Stack Web Development Certificate A 12-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills for Full Stack Web Development using Javascript. • Completion: June 2021

Columbia College Chicago • Chicago, IL • Graduation: May 2017 • Cumulative GPA: 3.8/4.0 Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Audio Engineering • Minor: Management

Huntley High School • Huntley, IL • Graduation: June 2013

Technical Skills:

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React JS, JQuery, Node JS, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars JS, Bootstrap, JQuery, APIs, Node JS, Insomnia, Git, and GitHub

Projects:

Employee Directory • Deployed Site: https://jdinh3.github.io/employee-directory/ GitHub Repository: https://github.com/jdinh3/employee-directory

- A searchable and sortable directory of employees.
- Technologies used: React JS, Random User API, Bootstrap

Space Dashboard • Deployed Site: https://joshwrightdev.github.io/Project-1/ GitHub Repository: https://github.com/Joshwrightdev/Project-1

- A web application designed for space hobbyists to keep up with current astronomical events.
- Core responsibilities included styling and formatting of the site, and retrieving information from the NASA API to create a carousel of rover images.
- Technologies used: Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Google Fonts, JQuery, multiple NASA API endpoints.

Work Experience:

Aerotek • Engineering Recruiter • Schaumburg, IL • October 2020 – March 2021

- Identified qualified candidates through various recruiting and sourcing tools
- Screened and interviewed qualified candidates for different engineering roles
- Built relationships with industry contacts to gain knowledge and generate referrals and sales leads

• PSAV

Sales Manager • Loews Vanderbilt Hotel • June 2019 – March 2020

- Consulted clients on audio visual needs for their conferences.
- Followed clients' specific requests to ensure excellent customer service experience.
- Built rapport and maintained healthy customer relationships.

Sales Coordinator • Gaylord Opryland Resort • June 2018 – June 2019

AV Technician • Loews Chicago Hotel • November 2016 – June 2018

- Set up audio, video and lighting equipment according to clients' needs
- Troubleshooted and fixed technical problems on-site.